<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sysoft</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="about_desc">Sysoft technology as a premier technical institute in town, established in the year 2002 with handful of students. In course of time within two to three years a massive batch of students have undergone in different courses like oracle, .net, java, c, c++, hardware and networking and have been secured placement efficiently in companies like Infosys, TCS, TechMahindra, HCL, Oracle Finance, Accenture and many more. Our primary objective is empowerment through proper knowledge because young minds can be developed through proper education. The organization runs on the belief that we educate and help the students to acquire a technical expertise</string>
    <string name="wallk">We not just show students the right path but walk with them untill they can walk by their own</string>
    <string name="about">About Instaminds Technologies and Outsourcing Pvt. Ltd</string>
    <string name="para1">InstaMinds Technologies and outsourcing Pvt. Ltd is an innovative platform for the job aspirant students. We work in the direction of assessment to opportunity and providing solutions. InstaMinds believe in value creation and taking part in problem solving. We work towards creating values in the direction of campus to corporate, assessment to associate. Our core team is market competent and having problem solving personalities, who are the real heroes of our company and taking part to lead from root to fruit.</string>
    <string name="para2">Our INTERNSHIP is based on C2C [CAMPUS TO CORPORATE] model of Training Programs aims to build high level competency within individual to compete in the market. It would be a definite boost to their personal contribution and performance levels in the organization. This program is aimed to train candidates to the professional level for the job requirement of the organisation. Internship Programme is on Live E-commerce Portal.</string>
    <string-array name="spinner">
        <item>--choose subjects-- </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
